<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Edg.ist</title><link>https://edg.ist/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Edg.ist</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><managingEditor>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</managingEditor><webMaster>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</webMaster><copyright>Mike Parker</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://edg.ist/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuck working Mondays. I've got better things to do.</title><link>https://edg.ist/posts/fuck-working-mondays-ive-got-better-things-to-do/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</author><guid>https://edg.ist/posts/fuck-working-mondays-ive-got-better-things-to-do/</guid><description>Why I Don’t Work Mondays (And Maybe You Shouldn’t Either) — Monday is my reset button after a hectic weekend full of kids, football, and family chaos. No meetings, no commute, just space to breathe, walk the dogs and reconnect with me. It’s not lazy — it’s intentional.</description></item><item><title>The Design of Invisible Things</title><link>https://edg.ist/posts/the-design-of-invisible-things/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</author><guid>https://edg.ist/posts/the-design-of-invisible-things/</guid><description>What if we designed businesses like we design products—intuitive, human-centred, and easy to use? Exploring the early design of two new ventures, drawing on principles from The Design of Everyday Things to shape everything from culture to communication. Inspired by thinkers like Don Norman, Ricardo Semler, Jason Fried, and Paul Graham, it&amp;rsquo;s a blueprint for a simpler, smarter, and more empowering way to build a company—one that&amp;rsquo;s as much about how it feels as how it functions.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back Before Moving Forward</title><link>https://edg.ist/posts/a-look-back-before-moving-forward/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</author><guid>https://edg.ist/posts/a-look-back-before-moving-forward/</guid><description>After five years off the grid, I’m back with a renewed drive to build. Reflecting on my journey from founding Orange Bus to growing it into a global digital agency and navigating the chaos post-acquisition by Capita PLC. It’s a story of pride, frustration, corporate dysfunction, and the toll on creativity. Now, with the past behind me, it’s time to focus on building meaningful, enduring companies once again.</description></item><item><title>Liberty, Control, and the Business of "Free"</title><link>https://edg.ist/posts/liberty-control-and-the-business-of-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>mikeyparker@gmail.com (Mike Parker)</author><guid>https://edg.ist/posts/liberty-control-and-the-business-of-free/</guid><description>We’ve traded our privacy for “free” web services—but at what cost? Corporations and governments harvest our data, turning users into products in a vast surveillance economy. We’ve handed over control of our digital lives. What began as convenience has become corporate and state overreach. This isn’t just about privacy—it’s a battle between liberty and control. Wake up before it’s too late.</description></item></channel></rss>